planyo.com 2019-12-30

# Privacy

    Privacy Notice Table Of Contents:
    
    1. Our Commitment To Privacy
    2. The Information We Collect
    3. How We Use Information
    4. Where Is Information Kept and Who Can Access It
    5. Our Commitment To Data Security
    6. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy
    7. How To Access, Delete Or Correct Your Information
    8. How To Contact Us
    
    1. Our Commitment To Privacy
    
    Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online
    information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
    To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally
    identifiable information may be requested.
    
    2. The Information We Collect:
    
    This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Planyo website. The types of personal
    information collected are:
    
          Name
          Address
          Email address
          Phone/mobile number
          IP address
          [Planyo site admins can request other information on booking page]
    
    3. The Way We Use Information:
    
    We use the information you provide about yourself when making a reservation only to complete the reservation
    details. We never share this information with outside parties except the administrator of
    the resource/site you are reserving.
    
    We use the email address to send you important information related to your
    reservations such as reservation notifications and updated reservation
    status (configured by the site admin), or, if you are a site admin, 
    important information related to your Planyo site in general. The email addresses are not
    used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties except the administrator of the
    resource/site you are reserving.
    
    Some site admins can use your mobile phone number to send SMS messages
    related to your reservations.
    
    You can register with our website (with a login and password) if you
    would like to be able to easily manage your reservations and to have your
    personal information automatically filled out during future reservations.
    
    We may use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design and promote our website but we would
    not disclose anything that could be used to identify any individual.
    
    Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways
    unrelated to the ones described above.
    
    4. Where Is Information Kept and Who Can Access It
    
    The only entities having access to customers' personal information
    are:
    - Site administrator and moderators who are obligated by law (e.g. GDPR in the EU) to keep 
    the personal information safe and used for the clearly defined purposes
    - Xtreeme Sagl (creator of Planyo.com) headquartered in Lavertezzo, Switzerland
    - Amazon SES (US-East Region)
    We have agreements in place between Xtreeme Sagl (Planyo), Amazon SES
    and the European Commission which ensure the compliance with the GDPR policies.
    
    5. Our Commitment To Data Security
    
    To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have 
    put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the
    information we collect online.
    
    6. Our Commitment To Children's Privacy:
    
    Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never
    collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 16, and
    no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 16.
    
    7. How You Can Access, Delete Or Correct Your Information
    
    IF YOU HAVE A PLANYO LOGIN:
    You can access all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain
    by logging into your account and going to the My Account page. We use this procedure to better
    safeguard your information. You can delete your account on that page.
    
    IF YOU DO NOT HAVE A PLANYO LOGIN:
    Go to https://www.planyo.com/login/delete-info.php where you can
    request the personal information we keep on file to be sent to you for
    a review with a possibility to delete all your personal information
    from our databases. Note that if you have valid reservations in the
    future or with end date less than 60 days ago,
    you'll need to contact the site admin to have your personal
    information removed OR you simply have to wait at least 60 days after
    the rental time and request automatic removal.
    
    You can also correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us
    a request that credibly shows error. To protect your privacy and
    security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
    
    7. How To Contact Us
    
    Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email
    at planyo [at] xtreeme.com or by post:
    Xtreeme Sagl
    Via Cantonale
    CH-6633 Lavertezzo
    Switzerland
